diatomaceousearthaustralia.com.au 2019-03-07

# Diatomaceous Earth Australia Pty Ltd, Privacy, Food Grade Diatomaceous Earth Melbourne

Our Approach to Privacy

" **Diatomaceous Earth Australia Pty Ltd** " is herein called "The Company"  
"The Viewer" is herein called "You" or "Your"  
"By Law" herein refers to the laws of QLD, Australia.

The Company is committed to protecting your personal information and take your right to privacy very seriously.

This Privacy Policy is applicable to this website owned and operated by The Company.

You must read and accept all of this Privacy Policy before you may become a user of this website. By accepting this Privacy Policy you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

Overview

This Privacy Policy describes the information The Company collects about you and what may happen to that information. When you enter your information into a form on our website, The Company may collect personally identifiable information about you (your "Information"). Some of your Information may be disclosed to third parties and used by those third parties only if pertaining to work related enquiries. Whilst every attempt by The Company is made to endure your details remain secure when used by third party companies, we accept no responsibility for any action they cause either knowingly or unknowingly with your information.

We personally will **never sell or rent** your personal information to third parties. We are not responsible for your details if a second or third party needs to be involved and they manage your details.

If you do not agree to your Information being used or disclosed in this way, please do not use our website.

Information Collection

The Company may collect information from you including your email address, name and telephone number which will be necessary to provide our services. Should you contact The Company by email, telephone or send us correspondence, we may collect such information into a file which is specific to you.

Like many websites, The Company may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files, such as your IP address and occasionally, basic cookie information.

Cookies

We may or may not use cookies. By using this site you agree to allow us the use of any such cookies now or in the future.

Use of Your Information

The Company will use your Information to provide our services to you. You agree that we may use your Information to contact you for purposes including but not limited to discussing our products and services, maintenance, repairs or new products relevant to your use of this website. You agree that we may use your Information to track and target your interests in order to enhance your experience on our website, to improve our website content and services, customise our website's content and layout, analyse usage of our website and to improve our marketing efforts. We will use your Information in this way to improve our website and tailor it to better meet your specific needs.

Disclosure of Your Information

The Company will never sell or rent your Information to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. We will NOT aggregate the information you send to us with other data (so that you cannot be identified) and use that aggregated data for administrative purposes.

The Company may employ the services of third party service providers in certain aspects of our operations and to help us deliver specific services. Depending on the services performed, some of these providers may be provided with your Information and we will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third party service providers are obligated to protect your Information on your behalf.

Legal Disclaimer

Although The Company will make every effort to preserve users privacy, we may need to disclose your Information when required "By Law" wherein we have any legal court document(s) requesting The Company to release said information and that such action is necessary to comply with a current or pending judicial proceeding, ie: the court order, pertaining or not pertaining to any investigation or other of any possible unlawful activity or activity that may expose us or you to legal liability.

Unlike many companies, we do NOT release any such information "in good-faith". It must be requested By Law.

Security

We use reasonable endeavours to safeguard the confidentiality of your Information, to keep your Information secure and to disclose such information only as described in this Privacy Policy. We will hold and transmit your Information in a secure and confidential environment.

While all care is taken, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information.

Business Transitions

In the event that The Company is subjected to a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, your Information will be part of the assets transferred. Notification of any changes will be clearly listed on our website in the event of a change of ownership or control of your Information.

External Links

Our website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information from you.

This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on this website.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to amend or modify our Privacy Policy from time to time and such modification shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified policy on this website. You are responsible for regularly reviewing information posted online to obtain timely notice of such changes. Your continued use of this website after amendments are posted constitutes your acceptance of this policy as modified. If we make any changes, substantive or otherwise, to this Privacy Policy, we will announce it on our website.

Contact Information

Your privacy is extremely important to us. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our website, please feel free to [Contact Us](https://www.diatomaceousearthaustralia.com.au/Contact/index.php "Contact Diatomaceous Earth Australia Pty Ltd").
